Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Lord, something terrible has happened.
يا رب، لقد حدث شيء فظيع.
The corrupted ones have appeared again.
لقد ظهر الفاسدون مرة أخرى.
They disrupted the Fire Festival,
لقد قاموا بتعطيل مهرجان النار،
and nearly killed the three Young Masters.
وكاد أن يقتل الثلاثة أساتذة الشباب.
Corrupted ones?
فاسدين؟
Are they like me?
هل هم مثلي؟
Minister Huo.
الوزير هوو
How dare you barge into my chambers?
كيف تجرؤ على اقتحام غرفتي؟
Forgive me, Lord.
سامحني يا رب.
Corrupted ones appeared at the Fire Festival.
ظهرت الفاسدين في مهرجان النار.
We urgently need you to take charge.
نحن في حاجة ماسة إليك لتتولى المسؤولية.
What?
ماذا؟
Nonsense!
هراء!
Please calm down, father.
من فضلك اهدأ يا أبي.
Look at what you two have done.
انظروا ماذا فعلتما.
A perfectly good Fire Festival
مهرجان نار جيد تمامًا
has turned into chaos, with deaths and injuries.
تحولت إلى حالة من الفوضى، مع سقوط قتلى وجرحى.
It's a complete mess.
إنها فوضى كاملة.
I, Nan Feng, have been brave all my life,
أنا، نان فينج، كنت شجاعًا طوال حياتي،
yet my two sons are no better than useless.
ولكن ابنائي ليسوا أفضل حالاً من عديمي الفائدة.
Eldest brother.
الأخ الأكبر.
Father.
أب.
Father, please!
أبي من فضلك!
The corrupted ones appeared out of nowhere.
ظهر الفاسدون من العدم.
Everyone is terrified.
الجميع مرعوبون.
I was in charge of organizing the festival.
كنت مسؤولاً عن تنظيم المهرجان.
But the city's defenses
لكن دفاعات المدينة
have always been handled by my younger brother.
لقد تم التعامل معها دائمًا من قبل أخي الأصغر.
Who could pull this off right under my nose?
من يستطيع أن يفعل هذا تحت أنفي مباشرة؟
How could this happen?
كيف يمكن أن يحدث هذا؟
This is very suspicious.
هذا أمر مشبوه للغاية.
Someone must be plotting behind the scenes.
لا بد أن يكون هناك شخص يخطط خلف الكواليس.
They want to frame me, father.
يريدون توريطني يا أبي.
I beg you to investigate thoroughly.
أرجو منك التحقيق جيدا.
In my opinion,
في رأيي،
we should start by checking the defense personnel.
ينبغي لنا أن نبدأ بالتحقق من أفراد الدفاع.
Second brother.
الاخ الثاني.
Lord, the eldest Young Master...
يا سيدي، السيد الشاب الأكبر...
Zhusheng.
تشوشنغ.
Please calm down, father.
من فضلك اهدأ يا أبي.
My leg ailment has relapsed recently.
لقد عاودتني مشكلة ساقي في الآونة الأخيرة.
I've been unwell and neglected my duties.
لقد كنت مريضًا وأهملت واجباتي.
I failed to assist my elder brother with the ceremony.
لقد فشلت في مساعدة أخي الأكبر في الحفل.
I am willing to accept punishment.
أنا مستعد لقبول العقاب.
Reporting to my lord,
تقريرا إلى سيدي،
it was the eldest Young Master who ordered the second Young Master
كان الشاب الأكبر هو الذي أمر الشاب الثاني
not to interfere with the ceremony.
عدم التدخل في الحفل.
The second Young Master, to prevent mistakes,
الشاب الثاني، لتجنب الأخطاء،
specifically arranged guards around the area.
تم ترتيب حراس بشكل خاص حول المنطقة.
He was even injured while saving the eldest Young Master.
حتى أنه أصيب أثناء إنقاذه للشاب الأكبر سناً.
So that's what happened.
وهذا ما حدث.
So the second brother was lying in wait all along.
لذا فإن الأخ الثاني كان يتربص طيلة الوقت.
Such sinister intentions.
هذه النوايا الشريرة.
Father, you must investigate the second brother thoroughly.
يا أبتاه، يجب عليك التحقيق في أمر الأخ الثاني جيدًا.
Eldest Young Master, how can you turn on your brother?
أيها السيد الشاب الأكبر، كيف يمكنك أن تهاجم أخيك؟
After such a disaster,
بعد هذه الكارثة،
you did nothing,
لم تفعل شيئا
and even used a young girl as a shield.
واستخدم حتى فتاة صغيرة كدرع.
Now you want to frame the second Young Master.
الآن تريد تأطير الشاب الثاني.
Zhusheng, what nonsense are you talking about?
تشوشينغ، ما هذا الهراء الذي تتحدث عنه؟
Who do you think you are?
من تعتقد نفسك؟
Is it your place to speak?
هل هذا مكانك للتحدث؟
Enough!
كافٍ!
Stop arguing, this is disgraceful.
توقف عن الجدال، هذا أمر مخز.
If you two brothers act like this,
إذا تصرفتم أيها الأخوان بهذه الطريقة،
how can Xuan City be entrusted to you?
كيف يمكن أن تُعهد إليك مدينة شوان؟
I'm afraid you won't be able to protect it.
أخشى أنك لن تكون قادرًا على حمايته.
Please calm down, father.
من فضلك اهدأ يا أبي.
It's all my fault.
إنه خطئي كله.
I will do my best to investigate.
سأبذل قصارى جهدي للتحقيق.
Last night at the scene, we found
في الليلة الماضية، وجدنا في مكان الحادث
two suspicious outsiders.
اثنان من الغرباء المشبوهين.
They are highly skilled.
إنهم يتمتعون بمهارات عالية.
They might be involved in this incident.
قد يكونون متورطين في هذا الحادث.
Yes.
نعم.
Yes, exactly.
نعم بالضبط.
Those two are vicious and ruthless.
هؤلاء الاثنان شرسين وقاسيين.
They must have come to assassinate me.
لا بد أنهم جاؤوا لاغتيالي.
Senior brother.
الاخ الاكبر.
If you don't come down soon,
إذا لم تنزل قريبا،
your dear junior brother will be crushed.
سيتم سحق أخوك الصغير العزيز.
Little Radish.
فجل صغير.
It's not that I don't want to come down,
ليس الأمر أنني لا أريد النزول،
the problem is, I'm getting old.
المشكلة هي أنني أصبحت عجوزًا.
It's not good for me to soak in cold water.
ليس من الجيد بالنسبة لي أن أنقع في الماء البارد.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
You're getting old.
أنت تكبر في السن.
You can't handle much trouble.
لا يمكنك التعامل مع الكثير من المتاعب.
It's really cold.
إنه بارد حقا.
Xuan City's hospitality
ضيافة مدينة شوان
is truly terrible.
إنه أمر فظيع حقا.
They invited Master out of retirement,
لقد دعوا السيد للخروج من التقاعد،
yet they locked up his two beloved disciples
ومع ذلك فقد حبسوا تلميذيه الحبيبين
in this cold and filthy water prison.
في هذا السجن المائي البارد والقذر.
Madam Sun
السيدة صن
Sun
شمس
Why are you yelling in the middle of the night?
لماذا تصرخ في منتصف الليل؟
Madam
سيدتي
I...
أنا...
I'm scared.
أنا خائفة.
In this world,
في هذا العالم،
there's nowhere safer than this palace.
لا يوجد مكان أكثر أمانًا من هذا القصر.
Just have some water, you'll feel better.
فقط اشرب بعض الماء، وسوف تشعر بالتحسن.
Madam, this water is cold.
سيدتي، هذا الماء بارد.
Princess Yue,
الأميرة يوي
it's so late,
لقد فات الأوان
and I still have to light a fire to boil water.
ولا زال عليّ أن أشعل النار لغلي الماء.
That's too much trouble.
هذا الكثير من المتاعب.
Just make do and drink a little.
فقط اكتفي بالشرب والقليل.
Madam
سيدتي
I...
أنا...
What else do you want?
ماذا تريد ايضا؟
So troublesome.
مُزعجة للغاية.
Princess, are you hungry?
الأميرة هل أنت جائعة؟
Zhusheng
تشوشنغ
You silly girl,
يا فتاة سخيفة
all you care about is Zhusheng.
كل ما يهمك هو تشوشينغ.
You don't even have room for your brother.
ليس لديك حتى مكان لأخيك.
Second Brother
الأخ الثاني
You're such a bother.
أنت مزعج للغاية.
With someone like this,
مع شخص مثل هذا،
who has no family backing,
الذي ليس لديه دعم عائلي،
there's nothing to gain.
ليس هناك ما يمكن كسبه.
And still so picky.
ومازالت انتقائية للغاية.
Annoying.
مزعج.
Just trying to get you hot water.
أحاول فقط أن أحصل لك على الماء الساخن.
Madam Sun
السيدة صن
Is the water ready?
هل الماء جاهز؟
Almost, almost.
تقريبا، تقريبا.
I heard Madam's shrill laughter just now,
لقد سمعت ضحكة السيدة الحادة الآن،
I thought it was the sound of boiling water.
اعتقدت أنها صوت الماء المغلي.
No.
لا.
I... I didn't.
انا... انا لم افعل.
Oh my!
يا إلهي!
Can't even boil a pot of water.
لا أستطيع حتى غلي وعاء من الماء.
No use keeping hands like that.
لا فائدة من إبقاء اليدين هكذا.
Stop.
قف.
Why do you eat like that?
لماذا تأكل هكذا؟
This is the Princess's residence,
هذا هو مسكن الأميرة
can't it even fill your stomach?
ألا يمكنه حتى ملء معدتك؟
I heard there were monsters at the Fire Festival lately.
سمعت أن هناك وحوش في مهرجان النار في الآونة الأخيرة.
I've been having nightmares every night.
لقد كنت أعاني من الكوابيس كل ليلة.
Sometimes I sleep through the day,
أحيانًا أنام طوال اليوم،
and miss mealtime.
وأفتقد وقت تناول الطعام.
So there's no hot food left.
لذلك لم يتبقى أي طعام ساخن.
These useless servants...
هؤلاء الخدم عديمي الفائدة...
Second Brother
الأخ الثاني
Please don't stand up for me.
من فضلك لا تقف بجانبي.
You'll only get punished by father.
لن يعاقبك إلا والدك.
I'm not as brave and capable as you, Second Brother.
أنا لست شجاعًا وقادرًا مثلك، يا أخي الثاني.
You worked so hard for your position.
لقد عملت بجد للحصول على منصبك.
You fought for it yourself.
لقد قاتلت من أجل ذلك بنفسك.
Don't trouble father because of me.
لا تزعج والدك بسببي.
It'll only make him more worried now.
هذا سيجعله أكثر قلقا الآن.
But I can't let you suffer like this.
ولكن لا يمكنني أن أتركك تعاني هكذا.
Second Brother, your injury...
ثانياً أخي إصابتك...
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
Just a minor wound, it doesn't matter.
مجرد جرح بسيط، لا يهم.
Once I find out the cause of the corrupted ones,
بمجرد أن أكتشف سبب الفساد،
I'll ask father for permission.
سأطلب الإذن من والدي.
To marry you to a good husband.
ليزوجك زوجا صالحا.
And prepare a generous dowry for you.
وأعد لك مهرًا كريمًا.
When that time comes,
عندما يأتي ذلك الوقت،
I won't let you suffer at all.
لن أسمح لك بالمعاناة على الإطلاق.
Princess Yue
الأميرة يوي
The hot water is here.
الماء الساخن هنا.
Thank you, Zhusheng.
شكرا لك، تشوشنغ.
Second Brother is still injured.
الأخ الثاني لا زال مصابًا.
Take him back to the residence quickly.
أعده إلى مقر إقامته بسرعة.
Young Master
السيد الشاب
You insisted on seeing Princess Yue first.
لقد أصريت على رؤية الأميرة يوي أولاً.
The princess is perfectly fine.
الأميرة بخير تماما.
You can rest assured.
يمكنك أن تطمئن.
That guy named Dongqing must be tired of living.
لا بد أن هذا الرجل الذي يدعى دونغ تشينغ قد سئم من العيش.
He dared to hurt you, Young Master.
لقد تجرأ على إيذائك يا سيدي الشاب.
You messed with someone from the Princess's residence.
لقد تلاعبت مع شخص ما من منزل الأميرة.
Speak.
يتكلم.
Young Master.
السيد الشاب.
She deserves to die.
إنها تستحق الموت.
How could she do such a thing in Yue's residence?
كيف يمكنها أن تفعل مثل هذا الشيء في منزل يوي؟
Do you think I don't have enough problems already?
هل تعتقد أنني لا أملك ما يكفي من المشاكل بالفعل؟
There must not be a next time.
لا يجب أن تكون هناك مرة أخرى.
The chaos during the Fire Festival—
الفوضى خلال مهرجان النار؟؟؟
Young Master, do you suspect Zhusheng?
سيدي الشاب، هل تشك في تشوشينغ؟
If you suspect Zhusheng,
إذا كنت تشك في تشوشينغ،
Zhusheng is willing to prove his loyalty with his life.
تشوشينغ على استعداد لإثبات ولائه بحياته.
My people wouldn't do something so foolish.
لن يفعل شعبي شيئًا أحمقًا كهذا.
The walking dead that appeared during the Fire Festival—
الموتى السائرون الذين ظهروا خلال مهرجان النار؟؟؟
They had a strong scent of Zushima on them.
كان عليهم رائحة قوية من زوشيما.
A tiny amount of this can relieve pain and reduce inflammation.
كمية صغيرة من هذا يمكن أن تخفف الألم وتقلل الالتهاب.
But if you use even a bit more,
ولكن إذا استخدمت أكثر من ذلك بقليل،
it will numb the nerves.
سيؤدي ذلك إلى تخدير الأعصاب.
It causes madness and hallucinations.
يسبب الجنون والهلوسة.
It can even turn people into the walking dead.
ويمكنه حتى تحويل الناس إلى أموات يمشون.
More importantly,
والأهم من ذلك،
this substance is extremely valuable.
هذه المادة ثمينة للغاية.
One liang of the herb costs one liang of gold.
ليانغ واحد من العشبة يكلف ليانغ واحد من الذهب.
Zhusheng will investigate this matter right away.
وسوف يقوم تشوشينغ بالتحقيق في هذا الأمر على الفور.
And bring justice to the Young Master.
وتحقيق العدالة للسيد الشاب.
No need.
لا حاجة.
Is there any news about that girl?
هل هناك أي أخبار عن تلك الفتاة؟
Not yet.
ليس بعد.
I'll send more people to search for her.
سأرسل المزيد من الأشخاص للبحث عنها.
Besides,
بجانب،
we still have a trump card in our hands.
لا زال لدينا ورقة رابحة في أيدينا.
As long as she's alive,
ما دامت على قيد الحياة،
she will definitely come back for us.
إنها بالتأكيد سوف تعود إلينا.